October Kiss is a tv movie, comedy, romance film directed by Lynne Stopkewich.
Poppy Summerall is hired near Halloween as a temporary nanny by
Ryan Lawson, a widowed, work-obsessed executive.
Through a series of adventures, the eternally optimistic Poppy sets out to teach Ryan and his two young
children what is important in life - unconditional love, family and the joy of everyday occurrences.
Poppy and Ryan soon find they are drawn to each other.
Could it become more than temporary?
Poppy, played by Ashley Williams.
Ryan, played by Sam Jaeger.
Zoe, played by Hannah Cheramy.
Zach, played by Kiefer O'Reilly.
Abigail, played by Miranda Frigon.
Megan, played by Laura Mitchell.
Kiss is a 2019 Indian Kannada-language romantic comedy drama film directed by A.
Arjun and produced by V.
Ravi Kumar under Rashtrakuta Pictures.
It is the second Kannada-language film after A 2nd Hand Lover (2015) to be
inspired by the 2004 South Korean film 100 Days with Mr.
The film features debutantes Viraat and Sreeleela,
alongside Chikkanna, Sadhu Kokila, and H.
Dattatreya.
Kiss was released on 27 September 2019 to mixed reviews from critics
and became a commercial success at the box office.
The film was partially reshot in Tamil as Kiss Me Idiot in
2025, with Robo Shankar and Nanjil Vijayan.
The film explores themes of autumn, fall season, hallmark.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.